good morning good afternoon or good
早上好，下午好
evening depending on your time zone and
晚上取决于您的时区和
welcome back to the spring webinar
欢迎回到 Spring 网络研讨会
program I am Peter Humphrey your MC as
我是Peter Humphrey的节目主持人
always on today I am very excited to be
总是在今天，我很高兴成为
joined by one of my spring team
由我的一个 Spring 团队加入
colleagues Ryan Baxter who is on the
同事Ryan Baxter
spring cloud team works with a lot of
Spring Cloud团队与许多人合作
the Netflix open source folk in the
Netflix开源人士
present and in the future and he's going
现在和将来，他要去
to talk to you today about the upcoming
今天就与您谈谈即将到来的
spring cloud essentially which there's
基本上有 Spring 的云
already many milestone releases but
已经有很多里程碑式的发布，但是
looking towards a GA pretty soon on and
期待不久的将来成为GA
so Ryan maybe would you take a moment to
所以瑞安也许你想花点时间
introduce yourself and and then we'll
介绍自己，然后我们将
get into the meat of the presentation
深入演讲的内容
yeah sure so as Peter said hi my name is
是的，可以肯定，正如彼得说的，我叫
Ryan vector I do work on spring cloud
我在 Spring Cloud 上工作的瑞恩矢量
team mostly focused on kind of course
团队主要专注于某种课程
spring cloud components Netflix can fix
Netflix可以修复的 Spring Cloud 组件
your gateway stuff like that that's
您的网关之类的东西是
pretty much my deal awesome all right
我的交易几乎很棒
well let's let's let's get into it you
好吧，让我们开始吧，你
want to we're going to talk today about
想我们今天要谈论
some reactive micro services right with
一些反应式微服务
with spring clouds essentially so um
基本上有 Spring 的乌云
yeah I'm also very curious to hear a
是的，我也很好奇听到
little bit about the the reactive bits
关于电抗位的一点点
but um you know I think there's still a
但嗯，你知道我认为仍然有一个
lot of people curious about you know
很多人对你感到好奇
just API gateway in general so yeah
一般只是API网关，所以
let's uh take it away mister mr. Ryan
让我们把它拿走吧先生先生。瑞安
sounds good okay so like Peter said
听起来还不错，就像彼得说的
we're going to be talking about building
我们将要谈论建筑
reactive micro services with spring
Spring 的反应式微服务
cloud Finchley so that's going to be the
云Finchley，所以这将是
topic today if you want to get in touch
如果您想取得联系，今天就来
with me pretty easy to find on the
和我在一起很容易找到
Internet I'm at Ryan jbaxter on Twitter
互联网我在Twitter上的Ryan jbaxter
a web page at Ryan jbaxter comm of
Ryan jbaxter comm的网页
course if you have any questions
当然，如果您有任何疑问
regarding spring cloud stack overflow or
关于 Spring Cloud 堆栈溢出或
jitter is a good place to reach out we
抖动是联系我们的好地方
besides myself and my teammates were
除了我自己和我的队友
always there to help answer any
总是在那里帮助回答任何
questions problems you know feel free
问题，您知道的问题随时随地
open issues on on github in this room
在这个房间的github上打开问题
cloud projects role is longing to help
云项目角色渴望提供帮助
so yep that's the best place to get in
是的，那是进入的最佳地点
touch with me if you me after the
如果你之后我与我联系
presentation feel free to ask any
演示文稿随时问任何
questions at the end of the presentation
演讲结束时的问题
as well which would be awesome so I'm
太棒了，所以我
going to answer the number one question
要回答第一题
that probably everyone has if you're
如果你是
attending this presentation is one will
参加这个演讲是一个意志
spring confidentially be released right
Spring 秘密地被释放了
as Peter said we have a number we've had
就像彼得说的，我们有一个号码
a number of milestones I believe up till
我相信许多里程碑
this point we actually just a couple
这一点我们实际上只是几个
weeks ago released our first release
几周前发布了我们的第一个版本
candidate so the answer to your question
候选人，所以你的问题的答案
is actually all in the open we don't
其实都是公开的
hide anything you can head to the spring
隐藏任何可以前往 Spring 的东西
cloud releases or spring cloud release
云发布或 Spring Cloud 发布
project on github the URLs right there
在github上的项目URL在那里
and if you go to the milestones in that
如果你去那个里程碑
project you'll see our plan as far as
项目，您将看到我们的计划
when the release is going to happen so
当发布即将发生时
as ever things are very fluid so the
一如既往的事情是非常流畅的，所以
screenshot I have here which I took last
屏幕快照我在这里有我最后拍的
night at about 8 o'clock Eastern
东部时间晚上8点左右
Standard Time it has already outdated
它已经过时的标准时间
but we decided to change things a little
但是我们决定稍微改变一下
bit more this morning and our team
今天早上和我们的团队多一点
meeting we're going to do another
会议，我们将要做另一个
rc2
rc2
so we were planning to just do one we
所以我们打算只做一个
scan it and then go straight to the
扫描它，然后直接去
release but due to some changes in
发布，但由于某些更改
spring but-- we decided to do and some
Spring ，但是-我们决定去做一些
other changes that we know we have
我们知道的其他变化
coming in we decided to do another
进来，我们决定再做一个
release candidate so that release can
发布候选版本，以便发布
probably be released next weekend next
大概下个周末下映
week beginning of the week after so BRC
如此BRC之后的下周开始
- and there's potential for an RC 3
-RC 3的潜力
based on how that release can't go so
根据该版本的发行情况
more unlikely the ga release of Finchley
Finchley的ga版本发布的可能性较小
will happen in June at this point but we
将会在六月份发生
have a at least one other release
至少还有一个版本
candidate planned and then a following
计划好的候选人，然后是跟随的
maybe a another at least Canada after
也许至少在加拿大之后
that as well
那个
but keep track by going to this URL here
但请在此处转到此URL进行跟踪
in the leases project like I said
在我所说的租赁项目中
whenever we make changes to our release
每当我们对发布进行更改时
dates we put that all there so everyone
约会，我们把所有东西都放在那里
can see what's happening okay so some of
可以看到发生了什么事，所以一些
the things we're going to talk about
我们要谈论的事情
today basically I have a couple of
今天基本上我有几个
slides here not too many slides but
这里的幻灯片不是太多，但是
we're going to talk about some of the
我们将谈论一些
key enhancements to some of the projects
一些项目的关键改进
that that have been made and that will
已经做出的并且将会
be made in the spring club eventually
最终在 Spring 俱乐部制作
release we'll spend a little bit of time
发布，我们会花一点时间
talking about the spring cloud gateway
谈论 Spring 的云网关
because that is a new project that is
因为那是一个新项目
part of this forum Club function we
此论坛俱乐部功能的一部分，我们
release and then we'll do a little bit
释放，然后我们会做一点
of demo some coding and hopefully spend
演示一些编码并希望花费
some time with some Q&amp;A so get into the
需要一些时间进行问答，所以请进入
slides here so just a little bit about
在这里滑动，所以只是一点点
spring cloud Finchley if you're not
如果你不是 Spring 的云芬奇利
familiar with it already you make them
已经熟悉了，就让他们
poked around the code I hope you have
戳代码，我希望你有
actually and I appreciate if you have
实际上，如果您有
and opened issues and github but those
并打开了问题和github，但那些
that you don't know spring Club
你不知道 Spring 俱乐部
essentially is built upon project
本质上是建立在项目之上的
reactors Spring Framework 5 in spring
Spring 的反应堆Spring Framework 5
group 2.0 so you cannot use essentially
组2.0，因此您本质上不能使用
with you know a spring boot one 5x
你知道一个 spring boot 5倍
release you have to be using the latest
发布您必须使用最新的
spring to release and you know we take
Spring 释放，你知道我们采取
advantage of a lot of the reactor pieces
很多反应堆的优点
that are available now from Posche
现在可以从Posche获得
returns from framework 5 so that's just
从框架5返回的就是
a little bit about the architecture what
关于架构的一点点
we're building upon nothing has changed
我们建立在一切都没有改变的基础上
there we've always been dependent on
那里我们一直都依赖
boot we just decide to be excessively
启动，我们只是决定要过度
dependent on pututo
依赖于pututo
in the functionaries so because we are
在工作人员中，因为
taking advantage of a lot of the
利用很多
reactive pieces underneath us in the
在我们下面的反应性碎片
stack you'll see a lot of changes as the
堆栈中，您会看到很多变化
various projects that involve taking
涉及项目的各种项目
advantage of some of those things so for
这些东西的优势，所以对于
example
例
with sprinkled bolts we now have a
洒上螺栓，我们现在有了
reactive bolt template which provides a
反应螺栓模板可提供
reactive API for interacting with vaults
与保管库互动的反应式API
in addition we added support for vault
此外，我们增加了对保管库的支持
database backends where vault will
库将在其中存储的数据库后端
create connections for your applications
为您的应用程序创建连接
any applications can retrieve those
任何应用程序都可以检索那些
credentials from vault for your database
Vault的数据库凭证
services one of the cool features that I
服务我很酷的功能之一
think with that it was support for
认为这是对
spring data's repository concepts on top
Spring Data的存储库概念放在顶部
of alt so just like you can create a
就像您可以创建一个
repository for a Mongo database or you
Mongo数据库或您的存储库
know any other type of database you can
知道您可以使用的任何其他类型的数据库
now create a repository interface on top
现在在顶部创建一个存储库界面
of vault for retrieving credentials for
用于检索凭证的保险库
example from bulk and we've also added
大量的示例，我们还添加了
support for authentication with fault
支持故障认证
using kubernetes service account token
使用kubernetes服务帐户令牌
so spring cloud sleuths so marcin Han
如此 Spring Cloud Sleuth ，如此mar汉
and Adrienne if you know them they're
和艾德丽安（Adrienne）如果你知道他们
both involved in this booth project and
都参与了这个展位项目
again they've been quite busy with their
他们又很忙
work in solution Zipkin they basically
他们基本上在解决方案Zipkin中工作
decided this wasn't a decision that
认为这不是一个决定
happened great at the beginning of our
在我们开始的时候发生的很棒
planning but kind of in the middle of
规划，但有点像
spring cloud pinchy that they're going
他们要去的 Spring 的云朵
to rewrite sleuth using brave so it was
用勇敢重写侦探，所以
quite the undertaking and they had a lot
相当多的事业，他们有很多
of work ahead of them
他们前面的工作
and they did an excellent job of getting
他们在获得
all that done plus more on top of that
所有完成的工作以及最重要的是
so smooth now uses brave as its tracing
如此平滑现在使用勇敢作为其追踪
framework implementation so smooth no
框架实现如此顺利否
longer take care of storing the the
不再需要保存
context for the tracing it delegates all
跟踪的上下文将所有内容委派给
that to brave underneath so it's been
勇敢的在下面所以
quite a change for
相当大的改变
the internal salute there is a migration
内部敬礼有迁移
guide because there are several things
指导，因为有几件事
that are a little bit different now
现在有点不同了
since we are using braids so Marcin has
因为我们使用辫子，所以Marcin有
done a good job putting together Marcin
把Marcin放在一起做得很好
manger and have done a good job getting
马槽，并做得很好
to this migration guide explaining the
本迁移指南说明了
differences and changes so if you are a
差异和变化，所以如果你是一个
smooth user and you're looking to move
流畅的用户，您正在寻找移动
your application to Spring clubs in
您的申请到 Spring 俱乐部
Chile I suggest that you take a look at
智利，我建议你看看
that migration guide and and use that as
该迁移指南，并将其用作
you as you were applications over so
您就像您过去的申请那样
like I said besides that they they've
就像我说的，除了他们
added a bunch of other nice
添加了一堆其他漂亮的东西
functionality to sleuth and there's a
侦听功能，有一个
whole bunch more stuff that's not it
一堆更多的东西不是吗
actually when I had Marcin to kind of
其实当我让Marcin来
summarize the changes in sleuth for for
总结侦探的变化
the webinar he gave me a laundry list of
在网络研讨会上，他给了我一份洗衣清单
stuff so I had to whittle it down to
的东西，所以我不得不减少到
just try to fit everything on one slide
只是尝试将所有内容放到一张幻灯片上
so there's now support for tracing when
因此现在支持跟踪
you use the web client from web bucks
您从Web bucks使用Web客户端
so that's some more of the reactive bits
所以这是更多的反应性位
also with Nettie's HTTP client and
以及Nettie的HTTP客户端和
that's going to come into play when we
当我们
talk a little bit about the spring cloud
谈谈 Spring 的云
gateway and the apache httpclient
网关和apache httpclient
so if you're using any of those in your
因此，如果您正在使用其中的任何一个
new spring boot to doto apps we now will
新的 spring boot 到doto应用程序，我们现在将
add tracing to those patient lines
向这些患者行添加跟踪
so we also now have added some new
所以我们现在也添加了一些新的
support for messaging tracing tracing
支持消息跟踪跟踪
with men's tracing with messaging so we
用消息追踪男人，所以我们
have support for spring Kafka and spring
支持 Spring 卡夫卡和 Spring
RabbitMQ in addition we've added support
RabbitMQ另外我们还增加了支持
for Amazon x-ray and Apache do globe as
适用于Amazon X射线和Apache，
well so a few uses of those applications
那么这些应用程序的一些用途
you can take advantage of that stuff ok
你可以利用这些东西好
in contract again there's a lot more
在合同中，还有更多
than I was able to fit on the slide I
比我能装在幻灯片上
just highlights here we're gonna kind of
只是这里的重点
briefly touch on some of this stuff in
简要介绍一下其中的一些内容
the demo but we have support for a rest
演示，但我们有休息的支持
assured with rest Doc's support for
放心Doc的支持
packs the
包装
ranee with pac broker one of the
ranee与pac经纪人之一
features but i kind of like the net are
功能，但我有点像网
the next two so the utilities upload and
接下来的两个，以便实用程序上传并
fetch stubs from a git repository as
从git仓库中获取存根为
opposed to always using maven and then
反对总是使用Maven然后
the ability to find contracts in the
在合同中找到合同的能力
amal where previously you could only
阿马尔以前只能在哪里
define contracts and groovy I'm not much
定义合同和常规我不是很多
of a groovy user myself so I use more
自己的习惯，所以我使用更多
familiar the Amal so I like the ability
熟悉阿马尔（Amal），所以我喜欢这种能力
to do that and if you are interested in
这样做，如果您有兴趣
using contract with other languages
使用其他语言的合同
there are now docker images available
现在有可用的docker映像
that are can be used for polyglot
可以用于多语种
support so if you're using node.js for
支持，因此，如果您使用的是node.js
example then you want to use from cloud
示例，然后您想从云中使用
contracts that you can now take
您现在可以接受的合同
advantage of these docker images that
这些docker映像的优势在于
are available for polyglot support just
仅可用于多语种支持
lyin ensure that we yeah um would you
lyin确保我们是的，你会
just for our listeners that might not be
只为我们的听众
familiar with spring cloud contract
熟悉Spring Cloud Contract
could you give like maybe a two sentence
你能给我大概两句话吗
sort of you know what is it sort of
有点你知道那是什么
thing just for it for anyone that maybe
只是为任何可能的人准备的东西
doesn't know sure so typically when you
通常不知道这样确定
take a look at your micro services
看看您的微服务
architecture you're going to have you
建筑将要你
know this kind of dependency tree where
知道这种依赖树在哪里
one micro servers depend on information
一台微型服务器取决于信息
another microservice which depends on
另一个依赖于的微服务
information from another microservice
来自另一个微服务的信息
right so when it comes down to testing
是的，所以当涉及到测试时
these things lots of times you as you
这些事情很多时候像你一样
know the micro servers be that consumes
知道微服务器是消耗
micro service a you kind of mock up the
微服务，您可以模拟
functionality that you believe is
您认为是的功能
present in mark micro service a so you
存在于标记微服务中，因此您
can run tests against the functionality
可以针对功能运行测试
and your micro service that you're
和您的微服务
building and that's all fine and good
建筑，一切都很好
but when the team that owns a micro
但是当拥有微型车的团队
server is a goes ahead and changes
服务器是一个前进和变化
something about their api or whatever
关于他们的api之类的信息
you may not know about it and often your
您可能不知道，通常您
tests are passing fine you know but in
测试通过得很好，你知道，但是
production everything starts to break
生产一切开始中断
down
下
so idea with
这样的想法
contract is that you know micro serves a
合同是你知道微服务
produces contracts about its
产生有关其的合同
functionality in that way if you're a
如果您是
consumer of microserver say you can
微型服务器的消费者说可以
consume those contracts and you have you
消耗那些合同，你有你
know knowledge about what the
知道什么
expectations are right so instead of you
期望是正确的，所以代替你
interpreting the functionality of micro
解释微型功能
serves a to run your test you're
用于运行您的测试
actually using contracts are published
实际使用合同已发布
by that micro service to run your tests
通过该微服务运行您的测试
against right so if the team that owns
反对权利，所以如果拥有的球队
market serves a and this model goes
市场服务一个，这种模式去
ahead and change something and changes
前进，改变并改变
some functionality they change their
他们改变了一些功能
test make all the tests pass so when
测试使所有测试通过
they publish these new contracts well
他们很好地发布了这些新合同
awesome your tests are going to start
很棒的测试即将开始
failing because there's some new
失败，因为有一些新
expectation that you weren't aware of
期望您没有意识到
and now everyone knows about it right so
现在每个人都知道这一点，所以
there's just kind of nice communication
那里的交流很好
between consumers and producers that is
在消费者和生产者之间
in this market services environment so
在这种市场服务环境中
it it definitely helps out as far as
它绝对可以帮助到
testing and some complex new
测试和一些复杂的新
architectures okay next up sprint cloud
架构还可以，下一个sprint云
Netflix so not too many new features
Netflix，所以没有太多新功能
here just a lot of kind of clean up
这里只是很多清理
housekeeping type of things that we've
我们已经整理的东西
kind of been lingering around the
一直徘徊在
previous releases that we have a chance
我们有机会发布以前的版本
to make some significant changes now in
现在进行一些重大更改
2.0 so there's a new history stream
2.0，因此有了新的历史记录流
endpoint that can be used for web flux
可用于卷筒纸流量的端点
for apps so it's a reactive endpoint if
对于应用程序，因此它是一个反应性端点
you're consuming information about
您正在消费有关
history there's also a new clusters
历史上还有一个新的集群
endpoint so if your turbine user and you
因此，如果您的涡轮机用户和您
want to find information about but the
想要查找有关但的信息
the clusters are available to turbine
集群可用于涡轮
you can use this endpoint to to find out
您可以使用此端点来找出
more about that information I think
我认为有关该信息的更多信息
we've heard I believe actually there was
我们听说我相信实际上
a webinar yesterday about about my
昨天关于我的网络研讨会
micrometer so we're taking advantage of
千分尺，所以我们正在利用
micrometer in Netflix to to collect
Netflix的千分尺收集
metrics about Zul so some interesting
关于Zul的指标，所以很有趣
metrics collecting balls ool using
指标收集球使用
micrometer and these last two are more
千分尺和最后两个
just kind of migration things that you
只是你的一种迁移
should be aware of as you move from you
当您离开自己时应注意
know from Edgware or Dalston to spring
从Edgware或Dalston认识到 Spring
eventually open fame which used to be or
最终曾经是
fain used to be part of the Netflix
fain曾经是Netflix的一部分
open-source umbrella but I was recently
开源伞，但是我最近
moved out of that project into its own
从那个项目搬到自己的
github project so it's no longer under
github项目，所以它不再在
Netflix and so we've taken fain out of
Netflix，所以我们不屑一顾
sprint cloud Netflix and moved it into
冲刺Netflix云并将其移至
its own projects from comp Fame so it
来自comp Fame的自己的项目，所以
was no longer part of Netflix that's
不再是Netflix的一部分
more just a housekeeping housekeeping
只是家政服务
piece but does have some implications as
件，但确实有一些暗示，
far as your dependencies are concerned
就您的依赖而言
when learners appear a trained user also
当学习者出现受过训练的用户时
remove spree called Netflix AMQP and a
删除名为Netflix AMQP的大礼包和
lot of the starter actually all the
实际上很多入门者
starter modules that in that we're in
入门模块
spring cloud our Edgware and dolphin
Spring 的云，我们的Edgware和海豚
have been renamed and the old ones have
已重命名，而旧的已重命名
been removed so initially when you move
被删除，所以最初在您移动时
from an edge where our golf to released
从我们高尔夫运动的边缘到释放
to Finchley you might get a bunch of
到芬奇利，你可能会得到很多
problems in your Gradle or maven because
您的Gradle或Maven中的问题，因为
these starters no longer exist so just
这些启动器不再存在，所以
this slight naming convention here we've
这个轻微的命名约定在这里
gone from swinging clouds - starter to
从摇摆不定的云-入门到
spring cloud net flix starter instead so
Spring Cloud 网flix启动器反而如此
you just have to make some take some
你只需要做一些就可以
extra characters in your palm or your
手掌或您的其他字符
Gradle file to get things to work
Gradle文件让事情正常工作
properly all right
没事吧
was config not too much as far as new
配置不算太新
features here and provincially but one
这里和省级特色，但其中一个
of the cool things that we did add was
我们确实添加的很棒的东西是
support for database back-end so this is
支持数据库后端，所以这是
a long outstanding feature request that
长期出色的功能要求
was in spring cloud config for awhile
在 Spring Cloud 配置中有一段时间
you know he could use github or or
你知道他可以使用github或
subversion or file system or even fault
颠覆或文件系统甚至故障
for the back end of your config server
用于您的配置服务器的后端
but we've always gotten requests to
但是我们总是有要求
support data reason to the ball so now
支持数据的原因现在如此
we have a JDBC support so if you're
我们有JDBC支持，所以如果您
looking to use from cloud config with a
希望从云配置中使用
database you can now do that we've added
您现在可以执行的数据库操作
support for kiddie web hooks so if your
支持儿童网页挂钩，因此，如果您
kiddie is a different type of
小孩子是另一种类型的
cloud-based git repository so if your
基于云的git存储库，因此，如果您的
users are there those might be of
用户在那里
interest to you and we've added the
您的兴趣，我们添加了
ability to skip SSL validation for both
能够跳过两者的SSL验证的能力
get and vault back-end so if for
获取并存储后端，如果
whatever reason this can be somewhat of
无论什么原因，这可能有点
interests for in certain situations but
在某些情况下的利益，但
if you don't want to validate SSL
如果您不想验证SSL
Certificates
证明书
you can go ahead and skip that stuff in
您可以继续并跳过其中的内容
essentially release all right so sorry
本质上释放所有权利，所以抱歉
for screenshots a little hard to see but
截图有点难看，但是
we'll see this more on the demo so the
我们将在演示中看到更多
codes not so important but as you know
代码不是那么重要，但是您知道
there's a new web framework that's part
有一个新的Web框架
of spring fives so we had spring MVC and
Spring 五分之一，所以我们有 Spring MVC和
now we have spring web flux and you have
现在我们有了Spring 网通量，
a new web client where before we use
一个新的Web客户端，在我们使用之前
something like rest template to make
像rest模板这样的东西
HTTP requests now we have a web client
HTTP请求现在我们有一个Web客户端
and in Prior releases you can add is
在早期版本中，您可以添加
added the at load balance impatiens to
将at负载平衡impatiens添加到
your arrest templates to take advantage
您的逮捕模板以利用
of server discovery and load balancing
服务器发现和负载平衡的过程
client side load balancing
客户端负载平衡
and we've added functionality so that
并且我们添加了功能，以便
you can do now do the same thing with
您现在可以使用
your reactive web projects as well so if
您的反应式网络项目也是如此，如果
when you move to a more reactive
当你变得更加被动
programming model that will definitely
肯定会的编程模型
be abuse first from cloud users so look
首先要被云用户滥用
like i said we'll take a little bit
就像我说的，我们会花一点时间
deeper look at that in the demonstration
在演示中更深入地了解
as well and then lastly I'll talk a
同样，最后我会讲
little bit about our new project that's
关于我们的新项目的一点
part of the spring cloud Finchley
Spring Cloud Finchley的一部分
released so that is the spring Club
发布，所以这是 Spring 俱乐部
gateway this again is built on project
网关这又是建立在项目上
reactor spring five in spring moon 2.0
春月2.0的五号反应堆 Spring
and is the perfect use case for or I
并且是我的理想用例
shouldn't say perfect an ideal use case
不应该说完美的理想用例
for a reactive programming model so if
对于反应式编程模型，如果
you think about what an API gateway is
您考虑一下什么是API网关
it's you know the entry point for all of
您知道所有
your clients into your application right
您的客户进入您的应用程序权利
so there's a high amount of traffic that
所以有大量的流量
will be coming through this gateway and
将通过此网关进入
you don't necessarily you know you have
你不一定知道你有
this scalability problem so the more
这个可扩展性问题
traffic you have the higher you're going
您要走的流量越高
to have to scale your application so
必须扩展您的应用程序，以便
with the reactive model as I'm sure
我确定使用反应模型
we've talked about in previous webinars
我们在之前的网络研讨会中已经讨论过
you know this allows us to consume the
你知道这可以让我们消耗
reactive programming models the scoop
反应式编程为瓢建模
allows us to consume a lot less
让我们少消耗很多
resources when it comes to high traffic
高流量时的资源
applications so since this API gateway
应用程序，因为此API网关
is kind of a central focus for or will
是或将要成为中心重点
be a central focus in your architecture
成为您架构的重点
it's the perfect use case for while
这是一段时间的完美用例
using things like project reactor and
使用诸如Project Reactor和
what fluxes look like that so so we've
通量看起来像什么，所以我们
built the Gateway on top of these
在这些基础之上构建网关
concepts and the other the nice
概念和另一个很好
advantage here is besides being reactive
优点是反应性好
is that Spring web flux provides a lot
Spring Web助焊剂提供了很多
of functionality at the gate that is
在门口的功能
important for a gateway out of the box
对于开箱即用的网关很重要
so things like predicate so deciding
所以predicate这样决定
whether you're going to
你是否要
a certain request to a back-end service
对后端服务的特定请求
is important right so we can create
很重要，所以我们可以创造
predicates on a lot of different pieces
predicate有很多不同的部分
of information so things like headers or
信息，例如标题或
cookies or paths or you know the time of
Cookie或路径，或者您知道的时间
day that's the request came in right you
那天就是您的要求
can route based on anything about the
可以根据有关
request and that's a little bit
请求，这有点
different than if then if you're
不同于如果那时
familiar with using Zul so where is
熟悉使用Zul，所以在哪里
really going route based on path we have
实际走的路线基于我们拥有的路径
a lot of good functionality provided by
提供了很多很好的功能
webs locks out of the box that you can
网锁开箱即用
use a gateway the other thing that web
使用网关的另一件事是网络
flex provides is this this ability to to
flex提供的就是这种能力
apply filters to requests and responses
将过滤器应用于请求和响应
so if you need to modify the incoming
因此，如果您需要修改传入的
request or response in any way we have
以任何方式要求或回应
the ability to do that in the gateways
在网关中做到这一点的能力
you can do things like change the path
你可以做一些改变路径的事情
of add to header you can change response
添加到标题可以更改响应
bodies you can do anything you want
身体你可以做任何你想做的
manipulate the request response any way
以任何方式操纵请求响应
you really
你真的
please we also have the ability using
请我们也有能力使用
this functionality to to apply circuit
此功能适用于电路
breakers and do things like rate
破坏者，做诸如比率之类的事情
limiting and just a lot of cool
限制，很酷
functionality that just wasn't possible
不可能的功能
with something like Zul in the past yeah
与过去的祖尔一样
so we're going to take a kind of a
所以我们将采取一种
deeper dive into that being the
更深入地了解
demonstration I keep on wanting to use
我一直想使用的示范
my keyboard instead of clicking all
我的键盘，而不是全部单击
right so speaking of demo let's let's
对，所以说到演示，让我们
kind of jump into that let me know if
有点想让我知道
there's a problem seeing my screen it's
看到我的屏幕时出现问题
working
工作中
nope you're good so okay cool so okay I
不，你很好，很好，很酷，很好，我
am seeing actually online I am seeing oh
在网上看到我在看哦
there we go okay now it's starting to
我们现在可以开始了
come in it's a little there we go
进来一点点，我们去
we're good now sorry apologies okay um
我们现在很好，对不起，抱歉，嗯
so
所以
I'm taking we're going to start here
我带我们要从这里开始
with this at this pretty simple
这个很简单
application that actually my colleague
实际上是我的同事的应用程序
Marcin had written initially and there's
Marcin最初写过，有
just a couple things I want to point out
我想指出的几件事
about about it before
关于它之前
well we tell you a little bit about what
好吧，我们告诉您一些有关
the application does first so basically
该应用程序首先会这样做
this is a pretty simple application it
这是一个非常简单的应用程序
has a single endpoint called slash check
有一个称为斜线检查的端点
here in this controller and what this
在这个控制器中，这是什么
does is check whether a person is
是检查一个人是否
allowed to get a beer or not so you can
允许喝啤酒，所以你可以
see here this person checking service
看到这里这个人检查服务
and there's a API called should get beer
还有一个API应该叫啤酒
right so the implementation of that
是的，所以实施
service is this age checking person
服务是这个年龄检查的人
service here I've got a little bit
这里的服务我有一点
bigger where we can read and basically
我们可以阅读的地方更大，基本上
all this does is take a look at the
所有这一切只是看一下
person's age and if they are 20 or older
人的年龄，以及20岁或以上
they are allowed to have a beer but if
他们可以喝啤酒，但是如果
they are not 20 older they will not get
他们不大二十岁，他们不会变
a beer so real quickly I will gap does
这么快的啤酒，我会差距
be straightforward but I'll show you how
很简单，但我会告诉你
it works so let me just start the
它有效，所以让我开始
application up here should be running on
此处的应用程序应在
port 8080 and I'm going to terminal here
8080端口，我要去这里的码头
and we hit that endpoint so a de and
然后我们到达那个终点
we're going to make a post requests to
我们将向发布请求
localhost 8080 slash and we need to
localhost 8080斜杠，我们需要
include the age so the age is to you
包括年龄，适合您的年龄
should get your not okay to get beer
应该让你讨厌喝啤酒
right we have a status of not okay
对，我们的状态不佳
but if the age is 22 we see that the
但是如果年龄是22岁，
status is okay right pretty
状态还可以吧漂亮
straightforward nothing mind-blowing
直截了当
maybe mine willing but not to my look
也许我愿意，但我不看
now the one thing I'll point one thing
现在我要指出一件事
I'll point out here is that this is
我要指出的是，这是
using web bucks so you can see that
使用网络广告，这样您就可以看到
we're turning a mano here so just remind
我们在这里转马诺，所以提醒
you again there are two reactive types
你又有两种反应类型
mono influx and here we are
单声道涌入，我们在这里
returning a mono of type response right
返回类型响应权的单声道
so and that response is just okay or not
所以，这个反应还好吗
okay as we saw in the example all right
好，正如我们在示例中看到的
so now we have in this I'll point out
所以现在我们要指出
here we talked a little bit about some
在这里，我们谈到了一些
of the new functionality with sperm
精子的新功能
cloud contract here are the contracts
云合约这里是合约
within this dissipation actually written
在实际写出的这种耗散内
in yam all right so first before you had
在山药里好，所以首先
to use groovy like I said if you're not
像我说的那样使用groovy
too familiar with groovy it might be
对groovy太熟悉了
more comfortable amyl in that case you
在这种情况下，更舒适的戊基
can write your contract annual so here
可以每年写你的合同，所以在这里
we see just a quick example of what that
我们只是一个简单的例子
would look like as far as writing
就写作而言
contracts in the animal alright so we
没关系，所以我们
have a consumer of this API this check
有这个API的使用者
API and so take a look at that guy so
API，所以看看那个家伙
this also has a single endpoint which is
这也有一个端点
inside this Durer controller and the
在这个Durer控制器和
endpoint is that flash beer and
终点是啤酒和
basically this endpoint consumes a
基本上这个端点消耗一个
person object and it's going to call
人对象，它将要调用
that beer that check endpoint from our
检查我们终点的啤酒
producer let's check to see whether this
生产者让我们检查一下是否
person is allowed to have a beer or not
允许某人喝啤酒
so if they are allowed to have a beer
所以如果允许他们喝啤酒
right you get a status of okay back you
正确，你的状态还可以
get will return the string there you go
获得将返回字符串，那里你去
if not then you'll get the string get
如果没有，那么您将获得字符串get
lost right and the person object that
失去权利，人反对
where you consume just takes in a name
你消费的地方只是一个名字
and an age okay so what we're going to
年龄还可以，所以我们要
do here I'll just show you again quickly
做这里，我很快就会再告诉你
how this application works and then
该应用程序如何工作，然后
we'll start changing things around here
我们将开始在这里改变事物
so this should start up on port 8080
所以应该在端口8080上启动
riot ii-if run quick audience question
riot ii-如果运行快速观众问题
while you're booting up there will the
当您启动时，
API gateway support integration with
API网关支持与
Open ID Connect as configure as a
打开ID Connect，配置为
configuration so we are going to have
配置，所以我们将有
the same support that was available with
可以使用的相同支持
Zul which I believe
我相信祖尔
a wall so I believe that I think open ID
一堵墙，所以我认为我认为开放ID
can't remember exactly it open ID
记不清它的开放ID
connects supported oo or there's some
连接支持的oo或有一些
integration there but if it does then
在那里整合，但如果这样做
yes if not then we wouldn't support open
是的，如果不是，那么我们将不支持开放
ID connect out of the box but I'm not
ID连接开箱即用，但我不是
100% sure on that so if we go to and
100％可以肯定，所以如果我们去
we're going to make a posts 1 2 slash
我们将发布一个帖子1 2斜杠
beer and we're going to post a person
啤酒，我们要发布一个人
with the name Ryan and the age is 2 you
的名字叫瑞安，年龄是2
can see we get to get lost response but
可以看到我们迷失了回应，但是
if I'm 22 or 222 you see we said there
如果我是22岁或222岁，您会看到我们说过
you go ok so pretty straightforward now
你现在还好，很简单
the one thing I'll point out here is if
我要在这里指出的一件事是
we remember our producer was returning
我们记得我们的制片人回来了
was reactive right returned to a mono
是被动的权利回到了单声道
right but our consumer wasn't really
是的，但是我们的消费者不是真的
taking advantage of that they're using a
利用他们正在使用
using the rest template right
正确使用其余模板
traditional spring rest uncle which is
传统的 Spring 休息叔叔是
not reactive right so we can move this
没有反应的权利，所以我们可以移动
over now the one thing the other thing
现在，一件事，另一件事
I'll point out is that we are taking
我要指出的是，我们正在
advantage of service discovery right so
服务发现的优势就这样
this rest template if we look at the
这个休息模板，如果我们看一下
beam is load balance right so we can
梁是正确的负载平衡，所以我们可以
convert this over to be using web client
将其转换为使用Web客户端
which would support a more reactive
这将支持更积极的反应
programming model and we can take image
编程模型，我们可以拍摄图像
in the new at load balance what web
在新的负载平衡什么网站
client to do that right so we can go
客户做正确的事，所以我们可以去
ahead and start changing its around a
向前并开始改变它的周围
little bit so we're going to return the
一点点，所以我们将返回
first thing I need to do is change the
我要做的第一件事就是改变
pom actually so instead of using spring
pom实际上是这样，而不是使用spring
boots starter web we're going to use
启动我们要使用的启动器网站
spring dude and boot starter web clock
Spring 花花公子和启动启动器网络时钟
and we're gonna add a couple other
我们将再添加几个
dependencies here actually to Brad
这里的依赖实际上是布拉德
springing cloud starter sleuth yeah
Spring 云启动器侦探耶
springing starter sleuth Wow intelligent
Spring 起动器侦探哇智能
it just really not cooperating right now
现在真的不合作
Oh Artur smooth thank you
哦，阿图尔顺利，谢谢
and then we're also going to add spring
然后我们还要添加Spring
then can dark your starter okay so those
然后可以使您的入门者变黑好，这样
are all our dependency changes and we'll
是我们所有的依赖关系变化，我们将
go back to being we we're gonna create
回到我们要创造的世界
and now we can say a web client builder
现在我们可以说一个网络客户端构建器
and we'll change the meaning here
我们将在这里更改含义
instead of rust template to be builder
代替锈模板成为生成器
and then we are going to return a web
然后我们将返回一个网
client builder client so nothing new or
客户端生成器客户端，所以没有新内容或
crazy here the only thing we've done is
疯了，我们唯一要做的就是
added this at load balance annotation
在负载平衡注释中添加了此
which now supports what clients okay I
现在支持什么客户我可以
will add one more being here as in
将在这里添加一个
addition I want to do some tracing with
另外我想做一些追踪
smooth so I had a sampler being and
光滑，所以我有一个采样器
we're going to turn sampler sample okay
我们将把采样器的样本转好
that's pretty much the same as previous
和以前差不多
releases
发布
but you'll notice if we look at the
但您会注意到，如果我们看一下
imports that we're actually using brave
我们实际上使用勇敢的进口
instead okay so just a little bit a
而是好吧，所以一点点
little bit of a change there now if we
现在如果我们有一点改变
go back
回去
our controller here we're no longer
我们的控制器在这里，我们不再
taking in a rest template right we're
拿一个休息模板吧
gonna have a web client builder that's
将有一个网络客户端构建器
our being so we'll have a web client
我们的存在，所以我们将有一个网络客户端
builder will call it builder and then
建造者将其称为建造者，然后
our constructor also needs to be changed
我们的构造函数也需要更改
here so web client builder and just
因此，这里的网络客户端构建器只是
builder equals building okay so we still
建设者等于建设好，所以我们仍然
want to make the same kind of request
想要提出同样的要求
here that we were doing with the rest
在这里，我们正在与其余
template but we're going to use a web
模板，但我们要使用网络
client instead okay so here we are going
客户反而好了，所以我们在这里
to return builder build host URI and
返回构建器构建主机URI和
again same URI but since we're using a a
再次使用相同的URI，但是由于我们使用的是aa
load-balanced web client we're going to
负载平衡的Web客户端，我们要
the hostname is actually the the service
主机名实际上是服务
ID of our producer which is beer - api -
我们的啤酒生产商ID-API-
producer okay and then we need to post a
生产者好吧，然后我们需要发布一个
body so I never use body inserters and
身体，所以我从不使用身体插入器
from object and we're going to focus the
从对象，我们将集中精力
person here let's try to keep this a
这里的人，让我们尝试保持这个
little bit more readable and then we're
更具可读性，然后我们
gonna call exchange to make the request
要打电话给交易所提出要求
and then we're going to flatmap the
然后我们将平面图
response objects here and we are going
响应对象在这里，我们要去
to take the response and say the body -
做出回应并说出身体-
mono and the body the mono the type that
单声道和身体单声道的类型
we're going to use is response class
我们将要使用的是响应类
right so we have this so everyone's
对，所以我们有这个，所以每个人的
clear we have this response object for
显然我们有这个响应对象
the response right so that's what we're
正确的响应，这就是我们
converting it the body to and then we're
将其转换为身体，然后我们
going to flatten that bat and look at
弄平蝙蝠，看看
the response objects
响应对象
and we will say we're going to switch on
我们会说我们要打开
the response and if the case is switch
响应以及案例是否切换
no not respond still responds top status
没有不响应仍然响应最高状态
sorry case is okay then we are going to
抱歉，情况还好，那么我们将要
return mono just there you go just like
返回单声道就在那里，就像
we had before and if the Kate on the
我们以前有过，如果凯特在
default case it's like that default the
默认情况下，就像默认
fall then will return
下降，然后将返回
mono just get lost
单声道就迷路了
[Music]
[音乐]
everything's happy here
这里一切都开心
now we're no longer returning a string
现在我们不再返回字符串
we're turning on mono type string
我们打开单声道类型的字符串
instead and we don't need names code get
相反，我们不需要名称代码
rid of this and everything seems to be
摆脱这一点，一切似乎都是
happy again right alright so now just to
好吧，再次快乐，所以现在
reiterate we're using a web client
重申我们正在使用网络客户端
builder here a load balance web client
在此处构建负载平衡Web客户端
builder to make the same exact request
制造商提出相同的确切要求
here before to our reactive end points
在这里到我们的反应性终点
at slash check and returning a mono of
在斜杠检查并返回单声道
there you go instead of just the string
你去那里，而不仅仅是字符串
right or a mono if get lost instead of
对或单声道，如果迷路而不是
just the string all right so if we rerun
只是字符串还可以，所以如果我们重新运行
this lets you run the app here
这使您可以在此处运行应用
we should still see the same exact
我们仍然应该看到相同的结果
functionality if you start from there we
功能，如果您从那里开始，我们
go
走
I said intelligent if not being too
我说如果不是太聪明
happy with me right now is just moving
现在对我满意只是动容
very slow all right so we're still on
很好，很慢，所以我们仍然在
port 8081
端口8081
so we can make the same request see
这样我们可以发出相同的请求
there you go but if I am to get lost I
你去那里，但如果我迷路了，我
don't know sir what you mean this yeah
先生你不知道这是什么意思
so you get lost instead
所以你迷路了
okay so the API still working the way we
好的，所以API仍然可以按照我们的方式工作
want it to work
希望它工作
but now we're using project reactor
但是现在我们正在使用项目反应堆
instead so now one of the things we can
相反，现在我们可以做的一件事情
do here just to show and demonstrate a
在这里做只是为了展示和演示
little bit more or some new
多一点或一些新
functionality is we can put a gateway in
功能是我们可以放置网关
front of these two services right so
前面这两个服务对吧
let's go ahead and do that so I'm going
让我们继续做，所以我要
to create a new project here and using
在这里创建一个新项目并使用
Josh longs for place on the internet
乔希渴望在互联网上占有一席之地
spring initializer that's all fine and
Spring 的初始化，一切都很好，
good so we're going to add a couple of
好，所以我们要添加几个
dependencies here obviously we're going
依赖这里显然我们要去
to add gateway I am going to choose not
添加网关，我将选择不添加
to use good CUDA Oh God - I want to use
用好CUDA哦，天哪-我要用
actually that should be fine no let's
其实那应该没事的
hope that's fine
希望很好
gateway what else I want one Eureka for
我还想要一个尤里卡的网关
service discovery I want blue I want
服务发现我想要蓝色我想要
Zipkin I want maybe we'll play a little
Zipkin我想也许我们会玩一点
bit around with history depending what
随历史而变
we have for time but that should be good
我们有时间，但这应该很好
enough for now and I'm gonna put this
现在足够了，我要放这个
way - demo and right so create a new
方式-演示并正确创建一个新的
project here in a new window
在新窗口中在此处进行项目
and first thing I'm going to do here is
我要做的第一件事是
just rename my application properties to
只需将我的应用程序属性重命名为
application mammal because I prefer yam
应用哺乳动物，因为我更喜欢山药
over properties and you should too and
超过属性，您也应该
we're going to give our application name
我们将给我们的应用程序名称
so I don't like that bigger name gateway
所以我不喜欢那个更大的名字的网关
and I'm also going to set the port this
我还要设置端口
is going to run on because you already
将继续运行，因为您已经
have something running on port 8080 so
在8080端口上运行了某些程序
over on this on port 1990 instead all
在1990年的港口上
right and then we'll go to our
对，然后我们去我们的
application here and I'm going to create
这里的应用程序，我要创建
a couple beads so first being just like
几个珠子，所以首先像
before I'm going to create sampler so we
在我要创建采样器之前，我们
can trace some things Oh actually that
可以追踪到一些东西
reminds me I have to go back and make it
提醒我我必须回去做
another point about our other
关于我们另一个的另一点
application so just like in the producer
就像在生产者中一样
sorry in the consumer ordering to return
抱歉，消费者订购退货
the same type of Stan course before but
同一类型的斯坦课程，但
I just wanted to make the point here in
我只是想在这里指出
our consumer that as we'll see at the
我们的消费者
end with some of the tracing stuff that
最后是一些追踪资料
the tracing we are tracing requests made
我们正在跟踪所发出的请求的跟踪
from our web client so that was some of
来自我们的网络客户端，所以其中一些
the new support that we've added in
我们添加的新支持
Finchley to go with sloosh right so we
芬奇利（Finchley）坚持不懈，所以我们
can now support a single footprints in
现在可以支持一个脚印
addition to rest templates so back to
除了休息模板，所以回到
you yep ryan a couple couple questions
你是瑞安几个问题
um one was can we use fain as a reactive
嗯，我们可以用fain作为反应
client there um so no not officially so
那里的客户，所以不是正式的
there is some there is an open issue for
有一些开放的问题
that in spring cloud opens vein someone
在 Spring 的云打开静脉的人
has written some some on the community
在社区上写了一些
has written some code for that but it
为此写了一些代码，但是
hasn't been merged in
尚未合并
yet to to the master branch so if you're
还没有到master分支，所以如果你是
interested in doing that bets will work
有兴趣这样做的赌注将起作用
in progress I'm not sure if it will
进行中，我不确定是否会
happen before the release or the parent
发生在版本或父版本之前
depends on the contributor so which are
取决于贡献者，因此
interesting that you can look for that
有趣的是你可以寻找那个
issue in the open fame project and help
知名度项目中的问题和帮助
that along if you want
那如果你想
cool thanks phone sit I'm sorry good now
很酷，谢谢电话坐，对不起，现在好
it's going to ask if there's another
它会问是否还有另一个
question or market oh yeah um but
问题或市场哦，是的，但是
earlier someone was asking what is
早先有人问什么
reactive in this example but I think
在这个例子中是反应性的，但我认为
you've addressed that but then here yeah
您已经解决了，但是然后在这里
yep I can go back if there's no
是的，如果没有，我可以回去
questions but yeah um okay oh you're
问题，但是是的，嗯，哦，你是
back loose all right so we're gonna
背部松散，好吧，我们要
create another bean here and we're going
在这里创建另一个bean，我们要去
to turn a route locator and route
转动路线定位器和路线
locator builder so it takes in a route
定位器生成器，以便它采用一条路线
located builder and this is actually how
位于建设者，这实际上是
we're going to define our routes in this
我们将在此定义路线
example for the Gateway now I will say
现在以网关为例
that besides using this Java API that
除了使用这个Java API之外
there are two other ways to to define
还有两种其他方法可以定义
your routes so you could optionally
您的路线，以便您可以选择
define routes India in your mo
在您的手机中定义印度路线
properties your mo configuration as well
以及您的mo配置
or your properties your application
或您的应用程序的属性
configuration whatever you choose if you
根据您的选择配置
want to it doesn't make for a great demo
想要做一个不错的演示
so that's why I'm not going to do that
所以这就是为什么我不打算那样做的原因
but that's a perfectly valid way to do
但这是一种完全有效的方法
that there's also you could also define
还有你也可以定义
your routes in a database so any
您的路线在数据库中，因此
database that we have a reactive
我们有一个反应性的数据库
database connector for from spring data
来自spring数据的数据库连接器
you could define the routes and store
您可以定义路线并存储
them in a database and we'll pull that
他们在数据库中，我们将拉
information from a database back-end
来自数据库后端的信息
instead of either using a more Java
而不是使用更多的Java
configuration and like I said we're just
配置，就像我说的，我们只是
choosing to use Java configuration just
选择只使用Java配置
because it makes for a little better
因为它可以改善一点
demo but those are other options as well
演示，但这些也是其他选择
so here we're just going to return
所以在这里我们要返回
a builder dot routes build okay and we
一个建造者的点路线可以建造，我们
can start defining some routes here so
可以在这里开始定义一些路线，这样
if we want for example we can create a
例如，如果我们想要创建一个
route to our consumer apsr to our
通往我们的消费者apsr的路线
producer Avi and these routes take in a
生产商Avi和这些路线
predicate spec builder so this is how
predicate规范构建器，这就是方法
you're going to define some credit kits
您将定义一些信贷工具包
to decide where your requests are gonna
决定您的要求在哪里
be routed to so oops there's a whole
被路由到糟糕的地方
bunch of things you can use to help
一堆东​​西，你可以用来帮助
decide where things should go so you can
决定应该去哪里，以便您可以
route based on the path the host like I
基于主机路径的路由
said the time of day whether it's a
说一天中的时间是否是
cookie certain headers or president etc
Cookie某些标头或总裁等
etc so anything about the requests you
等等有关您的要求
can match on in route make decisions to
可以在路线上做出决策
our request based on that so in this
我们基于此的要求
example we'll just do if the path is
例如，如果路径是
slash check and well I'll show you
斜线检查，好吧，我会告诉你
another cool feature here is that you
另一个很酷的功能是
can use logic in your your predicate
可以在您的predicate中使用逻辑
mattress so you can say if the path is
床垫，所以你可以说路径是否
the last check and the host is something
最后检查和主机是什么
dot producer calm then we are going to
点生产者冷静，然后我们将
route to a URI here and the URI can be
路由到此处的URI，并且URI可以是
any or re-write any valid you or I but
任何或重写任何有效的您或我，但
in this case we want to use service
在这种情况下，我们要使用服务
discovery and in order to tell the
发现并为了告诉
gateway that we want to do that we're
我们要做的网关
going to begin with a special protocol
将以特殊的协议开始
lb right so lb stands for load balance
lb正确，所以lb代表负载平衡
right so we're going to say that we want
对，所以我们要说我们想要
to use load balancing and that this the
使用负载平衡，这
hostname that's going to come after this
之后的主机名
is going to be the this the service name
将是这个服务名称
of the service we want to route the
我们要路由的服务
request to so in this case it's beer
请求在这种情况下是啤酒
that number beer
那个啤酒
- thanks yai - the juicer and
-谢谢-榨汁机和
just so everyone knows I will just make
只是大家都知道我会做
a point of showing you that I do have
告诉你我确实有
Eureka running here so you can see we
尤里卡（Eureka）在这里跑步，所以你可以看到我们
have Eureka running in our consumer and
让尤里卡（Eureka）运行在我们的消费者中，
producer are registered in Eureka and I
生产者在尤里卡和我注册
will make this bit more readable I think
我认为这将使这一点更具可读性
let's see it all on screen here and then
让我们在这里在屏幕上看到所有
we'll define another route as well for
我们还将为
the producer so here we can see feed
生产者，所以在这里我们可以看到提要
path again we'll make the same path
再次路径，我们将走相同的路径
check actually make this even a little
检查实际上使这个甚至一点
bit more interesting for you and we'll
对您来说更有趣，我们会
route to the URI balance this is so much
路由到URI平衡这是如此之多
the API consumer okay so the way this is
API使用者可以，所以这是
going to work is if I make a request to
去上班是如果我要求
slash check and this host is actually
斜杠检查，此主机实际上是
present that animal route to this URI
呈现该动物路线到此URI
however if that post is not present and
但是，如果该职位不存在，
the path is check then we're going to
路径是检查，然后我们将
route to this your I said or this
路线到你我说的还是这个
service session said so let's give this
服务会议说，所以让我们给这个
a shot so if we run this
一个镜头，所以如果我们运行这个
right and we go - we're gonna go to 1990
对，我们去-我们要去1990年
and slash check and we're going to add a
和斜杠检查，我们将添加一个
host header here of the juicer calm and
榨汁机的主机头在这里平静和
post adjacent object of name and age -
发布名称和年龄的相邻对象-
you can see we got we went to our
你可以看到我们去了
producer service right so we got that
生产者服务正确，所以我们明白了
status not ok but if I change the age to
状态不佳，但如果我将年龄改为
22 we got that status ok so that seems
22我们的状态还不错，所以看起来
to be working so if I get rid of its I
工作，所以如果我摆脱它我
get rid of no come on and make every
摆脱没有来，使一切
type that yes so ok 1990 we're going to
键入，是的，好的，1990年，我们将
go to check is going to be Ryan in it
去检查将是瑞安
which is going to be - now we get a 404
将会是-现在我们得到404
back so why is that explain this because
回来，那为什么解释这是因为
it's kind of important so all the
这很重要，所以所有
Gateway is actually doing here is taking
网关实际上在这里正在采取
this request to slash check and it's
这个要求斜线检查，它是
going to forward it on to beer api
将其转发到啤酒api
consumer right it doesn't we don't have
消费者权利不是我们没有
a producer host so it's skipping this
生产者主持人，因此跳过了
doesn't match this right but it does
与这项权利不符，但确实如此
match this route because the path is
匹配此路线，因为路径是
just checked but it's just forwarding
刚刚检查，但只是转发
slash check on to be reg that consumer
斜线检查以注册该消费者
but your api consumer if you remember
但是如果您还记得您的api使用者
correctly it's path or that slash oh
正确是路径还是斜线哦
yeah sorry it's passing that slash beer
是的，很抱歉它已经通过了大刀阔斧的啤酒
right not slash check so
对不斜杠检查吧
we need to modify this request a little
我们需要稍微修改一下此请求
bit more so we're gonna do a little bit
多一点，所以我们要做一点
more magic here to get the gateway to
更多的魔术在这里通往
route things correctly so we can use a
正确路由，以便我们可以使用
filter to modify the requests right suit
过滤器以修改请求权
and say there's an example applying a
并说有一个例子
filter so it takes in a gateway filter
过滤器，因此需要网关过滤器
spec and here we can set the path rank
规格，在这里我们可以设置路径等级
so this is how we start manipulating in
所以这就是我们开始操作的方式
this case the request and in this case
这种情况下的请求，在这种情况下
we're going to set the path to slash
我们将设置斜线的路径
beer instead of slash check and just for
啤酒而不是斜杠检查，仅用于
the heck of it let's just modify the
它的内容让我们只修改
response to so we can add a response
回应，因此我们可以添加回应
header as an example so we can add this
标头为例，因此我们可以添加它
response header food with the value bar
带有值栏的响应标题食物
and the response that comes back so just
然后回来的回应就是
a just a couple examples of how you
只是您如何做的几个例子
might modify the request or response
可能会修改请求或响应
using the Gateway here so if we restart
在这里使用网关，所以如果我们重新启动
the app here Ryan as you're restarting
重新启动时，此处的应用程序Ryan
there was a question you know does
你知道有一个问题
reactive and this is a great question
反应性的，这是一个很大的问题
actually um the reactive implying using
实际上是反应式暗示
neti or can we use all this with Tomcat
neti还是我们可以将所有这些与Tomcat一起使用
yeah you can use it with Tomcat as well
是的，您也可以在Tomcat中使用它
so by default we do use neti as the
因此默认情况下，我们确实将neti用作
server in Gujarat oh but you can change
古吉拉特邦的服务器哦，但是你可以改变
it to be any server which I believe is
它是我认为是的任何服务器
Tomcat is one of them yeah all right so
Tomcat是其中之一，是的，所以
let's just try this again
让我们再试一次
so this time instead of sitting at 4 or
所以这次而不是坐在4或
4 we should get the response we're
4我们应该得到我们的回应
looking for which is get lost because my
寻找哪个迷路了，因为我的
age is 2 right so and if I changed my
年龄是2对，如果我改变了
age to be 22 they see there you go right
年龄为22岁，他们看到您走对了
so those are just some quick examples
所以这些只是一些简单的例子
here the one last thing I'll show you
这是我要告诉你的最后一件事
because we're getting it's almost been
因为我们得到的几乎是
an hour now so one last thing I'll show
现在一个小时，我要讲的最后一件事
you is some of the tracing right so the
您是某些追踪权的一部分，因此
reason why I wanted to do this here is
我想在这里这样做的原因是
because again one of the things that
因为这又是其中一件事
we've added
我们添加了
support forward spring closest is the
支持前向Spring 最接近的是
ability to trace the net ehm decline and
追踪净额下降的能力以及
under the covers that's what the Gateway
掩盖之下就是网关
is using so the Gateway is using the net
正在使用，因此网关正在使用网络
eh GB client so just by adding this beam
嗯GB客户端，所以只需添加此光束
here it means all of our requests from
这意味着我们从
the Gateway are going to be traced so
网关将被跟踪，因此
quickly we'll look and Zipkin here and
很快，我们将在这里查看Zipkin和
[Music]
[音乐]
you can take a look at the traces right
你可以看看痕迹吧
so we see a number of things tracing but
所以我们看到了很多事情，但是
we'll see that the requests are coming
我们将看到请求即将到来
from the gateway in this case right
从这种情况下的网关
here's that 404 that we got the first
这是我们得到的第一个404
time we configured our one of our routes
我们配置其中一条路线的时间
there where we configured properly it
在那里我们正确配置了它
wasn't rounding to the right place and
没有四舍五入到正确的地方，
see we've got a responsive world for but
看到我们有一个响应世界，但是
this is all being traced from the
这都是从
Gateway right and we can also see again
网关正确，我们也可以再次看到
traces coming from the the consumer etc
来自消费者等的痕迹
right so get all our tracing due to all
对的，所以要得到我们所有的追踪
that nice work and support and Asian
出色的工作和支持以及亚洲
clients that were added in smooth Ryan
在平滑Ryan中添加的客户
um yep is there another question is
嗯，还有另一个问题是
there the same concept as pre and post
之前和之后的概念相同
filters in Zul can we in Gateway as in
Zul中的过滤器可以像下面那样在Gateway中
Zul provide dynamic filters on the fly
Zul提供动态滤镜
I'm not sure what they mean by
我不确定它们是什么意思
on-the-fly they need to be configured
需要即时配置
right so here are examples of both a pre
对，所以这是两个
and a post filter right so here this
还有一个帖子过滤器，所以这里
pass filter is an example of a pre
通过滤波器是前置滤波器的一个例子
filter so we're applying we're setting
过滤器，所以我们要应用，我们要设置
the path of the outgoing request that's
外发请求的路径是
going to be made right from slash check
将通过斜线检查正确完成
to slash beer and this is an example
削减啤酒，这是一个例子
this ad response header here there's an
该广告响应标题中有一个
example of a post filter so this is
后过滤器的示例，所以这是
modifying the response after the request
在请求后修改响应
is being made I would get Oh sorry yeah
被制造我会得到哦对不起
everything on the fly like I would guess
像我想的那样，一切飞速发展
what they mean is that you know is there
他们的意思是你知道那里
is there like an actuator endpoint or
是否有执行器端点或
some way of modifying the pre and post
修改前后的某种方式
filter predicates by at runtime is my
在运行时筛选predicate是我的
guess but you know maybe the person you
猜猜，但你知道那个人你
asked
问
could clarify if they that's not in fact
可以澄清他们是否不是事实
it yes if that's if that's the case then
是的，如果是这样的话
the you know the way to do that stuff is
你知道做那个东西的方法是
to keep your route definitions in your
保留您的路线定义
llamo
拉莫
or your database and then take advantage
或您的数据库，然后利用
of refreshing the application using you
您刷新应用程序的过程
know the actuator and points to refresh
知道执行器和要刷新的点
the app and an update thing of adoration
该应用程序和更新的崇拜
that way so yeah you wouldn't want to
这样，是的，你不想
use it you wouldn't do one no you use
使用它，你不会做一个，你不会使用
Java configuration right so this is
Java配置正确，所以这是
purely just for really just for simple
纯粹只是为了简单
demonstration purposes you know I think
你知道我的示范目的
that the the more a better way to
越是更好的方法
provide the route configuration yeah
提供路由配置
more VA database um I have a question
更多VA数据库嗯，我有一个问题
that I've seen by the way I can confirm
可以确认的方式
that that our interpretation was correct
我们的解释是正确的
so we did no question as appropriate it
所以我们没有适当的问题
just brought up another question that I
刚刚提出另一个问题，我
think is probably in the minds of many
认为可能在许多人的脑海中
of our listeners um you know besides
我们的听众嗯，除了
yellow or properties like is there a
黄色或类似的属性是否存在
data store that tends to the best
最好的数据存储
practice you know get used when people
练习当别人知道时会习惯
do go the database route you know is it
确实走数据库路线，你知道吗
a Cassandra a popular option or like
卡桑德拉（Cassandra）受欢迎的选择或类似
what what do what do you see usage wise
你怎么看用法明智
or what do you expect I should say this
或你期望我怎么说
is still sort of preach a product but
仍然在宣讲产品，但是
what do you expect people to pair this
您期望人们如何配对
with if using a data store um I don't
如果使用数据存储，我不会
think we prefer one or the other I mean
认为我们更喜欢一个或另一个
we don't have any you know we don't lean
我们没有任何你知道的我们不瘦
one way or another we have a reactive
一种或另一种方式，我们有一个反应
connector for that database that's fine
该数据库的连接器很好
that doesn't matter to us that's really
对我们来说无关紧要
the only requirement so whatever your
唯一的要求，所以无论您的
datastore of choice is that's that's
选择的数据存储就是
good with us yeah prefer one thing over
对我们好，是，我喜欢一件事
the other cool just grace yep yes that's
另一个很酷的恩典是的，那是
all I had for the demo is there I'll put
我要演示的所有内容都放在那儿
up the back two slides real quick I had
后面两张幻灯片真的很快
one last slide but there are questions
最后一张幻灯片，但有疑问
other questions that be I did great but
我做的其他问题很棒，但是
again ways to connect with me
再次与我联系的方式
github Twitter my home page all my stuff
github Twitter我的主页我所有的东西
if you're looking for more information
如果您正在寻找更多信息
about spring cloud
关于Spring Cloud
you know we have our sperm cloud
你知道我们有精子云
homepage github repos etc samples tons
主页github repos等样本吨
of stuff like that and take a look at
像这样的东西，看看
the attachments and links section which
附件和链接部分
has links to all the repos that I talked
链接到我所说的所有回购
about and the code as well as a link to
关于和代码以及链接
the slide deck as well as your interest
滑轨以及您的兴趣
in that awesome Wow there are one
在那很棒的哇里面有一个
there's one more question but folks
还有一个问题，但乡亲
while you're while you're considering
当你在考虑的时候
what you've seen today and you are you
你今天所看到的，你就是你
know teeing up any last questions like
知道准备任何最后的问题，例如
Ryan said this is a good time to go into
瑞安说这是一个进入的好时机
the attachments and links section of
的附件和链接部分
your of your user interface and look for
您的用户界面并寻找
follow-up links although there's clearly
后续链接，尽管显然
a number of them on the slide as well so
幻灯片上也有很多
you know screenshot that or and/or
您知道该或和/或的屏幕截图
bookmark some of those other links down
将其他一些链接添加为书签
there if you're looking for more
如果您正在寻找更多
information I'm also we'd appreciate it
信息我也是我们将不胜感激
if you take a moment to rate the webinar
如果您花一点时间给网络研讨会打分
and maybe let us know what kind of
也许让我们知道什么样的
content you'd like to see in the future
您将来希望看到的内容
there should be a survey on involved in
应该对参与其中进行调查
that and and then you know realize that
那然后你知道意识到
you can come to spring one and learn a
你可以来 Spring 学习一个
lot more not just about spring cloud in
还有更多的不只是 Spring 的云
general but the rest of the entire
一般，但其余的全部
spring and Cloud Foundry DevOps
Spring和Cloud Foundry DevOps
infrastructures of service type
服务类型的基础架构
ecosystem and cloud native ecosystem
生态系统和云原生生态系统
that is going to be in September 22nd to
那将是9月22日至
2024 to 27th excuse me in Washington DC
2024至27日，请问我在华盛顿特区
on and there should be a banner
上应该有横幅
displaying across your screen now where
现在在屏幕上显示的位置
you can click the link and get a $200
您可以单击链接并获得200美元
off early bird discount which ends july
截止到7月结束的早鸟优惠
31st 2018
2018年31日
ryan will be presenting a spring 1
瑞安（Ryan）将出席 Spring 1
platform along with the you know vast
平台以及您所知道的广阔
majority of the spring team and lots of
The Spring Team 的大多数成员
other leading technologists on in fact I
其他领先的技术专家实际上
just learned a few days ago that we're
几天前才知道我们
going to have a decent chunk of the
将有一个体面的
Netflix open source team there at the
Netflix的开源团队在那里
event as well so we might be doing
活动，所以我们可能正在做
something special with them at the event
他们在活动中有一些特别之处
but at the very least there's going to
但至少要
be a bunch of Netflix and juniors
是一群Netflix和初级
wandering around as well um and yeah so
嗯，也是这样徘徊
excited for you to you know kick the
为您感到兴奋，您知道踢
tires on this whatever yet or
累了这个，还是
c1 or c2 um vs. Arce one right now and
c1或c2 um对阵Arce，现在，
RC - you wanna be some time RC - should
RC-您想花点时间RC-应该
be some time next week so fantastic okay
下个礼拜花些时间，好极了
so we love your feedback on those
所以我们很高兴您对这些问题的反馈
release candidates um and excuse me and
释放候选人，请原谅
um you know I think you know if you're
嗯，你知道我想你知道你是否
looking for four bit you know to do
寻找你知道要做的四点
usual maven and Gradle coordinates so
通常的Maven和Gradle坐标如此
you can just go to the spring project
你可以去 Spring 项目
page which there's a link - of course
有链接的页面-当然
right there on the slide and in the
就在幻灯片上和
attachments in the links section plug
链接部分中的附件插头
the coordinates into your maydel and
坐标进入您的Maydel，
grip maven and Gradle files if for some
握Maven和Gradle文件，如果有的话
reason you are you know stuck on some
原因是您知道卡在某些地方
sort of closed network you know you're
那种封闭的网络，你知道你是
in the military or you work for the
在军队中，或者您为
government or you're stuck behind 900
政府或您落后900
million layers of proxy servers for some
一百万个代理服务器层
strange for some reason you can get HTTP
由于某些原因而奇怪，您可以获取HTTP
downloads you know of this stuff we
下载您知道的这些东西我们
don't recommend it we don't really make
不推荐它，我们不是真的
it very easy for you to do that either
您很容易做到这一点
but you can do it it's possible you can
但是你可以做到的
get there to repo dot spring bio which
到达那里回购点春生物
is our nightly build our factory server
是我们每晚构建我们的工厂服务器
and you can get HTTP downloads of this
您可以通过HTTP下载此文件
stuff there we just don't recommend it
那里的东西，我们只是不推荐
because the experience is well not great
因为经验不是很好
um yeah so I think with that um let's
嗯，是的，所以我想
let's parse the last questions or - feel
让我们来解析最后一个问题，或者-
free to keep em adding stuff in folks as
免费让他们在乡亲中添加东西
we as we attend to this and just
我们在参加这个活动时
recognize that also this webinar is
认识到这个网络研讨会也是
recorded the slides will be posted along
记录的幻灯片将一起发布
with the webinar recording we very
通过网络研讨会录音，我们非常
highly encourage you to share this with
极力鼓励您与他人分享
your colleagues of the replay is
重播的同事是
available to you at the same URL that
您可以使用与
you use to register for this webinar is
您用于注册此网络研讨会的是
where the replay will be we also post it
重播在哪里，我们也将其发布
to YouTube if you happen to be one of
如果您恰好是其中之一，请访问YouTube
our youtube subscribers on so not not to
我们的youtube订阅者请不要
worry there but yeah great great thing
担心那里，但是是伟大的事情
to share with your coworkers especially
与您的同事分享
if you've been working with the Zul the
如果您一直在与祖尔（Zul）合作，
Netflix dual project this is something
Netflix双项目，这是东西
you're definitely you know if your other
你肯定你知道你的另一个
colleagues are working with it you
同事正在与您合作
definitely don't want to take a look at
绝对不想看
this as I think this is the the real way
我认为这是真正的方法
forward and for the future so Ryan one
前进和未来，所以瑞安之一
or two last questions on do all those
或最后两个问题要做所有这些
examples with the route locator can they
路线定位器的示例
be configured using yellow yeah
用黄色配置
so the one thing that you cannot do in Y
所以你在Y做不到的一件事
amel that I did do with the Java API is
我对Java API所做的努力是
to share my screen for you then is you
为你分享我的屏幕
can't do the logic so here where I ended
无法做到逻辑，所以我在这里结束了
these two credits together you could
这两个学分在一起，你可以
also do things like for or whatever here
也可以在这里做类似的事情
you know your logical operators but in
你知道你的逻辑运算符，但是在
the yamo configuration everything is
yamo配置一切都是
automatically ended together so all your
自动结束在一起，所以你所有的
products would be ANDed together and
产品将与在一起，
there's no option to do anything else so
没有其他选择
that's the only thing that you couldn't
那是你唯一无法做的
do in with a yellow configuration got it
用黄色配置完成它
ok awesome
好的很棒
um let's see okay and then there's one
嗯，让我们看看好，然后有一个
real question can the route locator work
真正的问题是路线定位器能否工作
without service discovery so Eureka yep
没有服务发现，所以尤里卡是
with just with just static service you
只用静态服务
are eyes yeah yep
是眼睛，是的
service cover is not a requirement it
服务覆盖不是必需的
was just I included as part of the demo
只是我被包括在演示中
today but that's definitely not a
今天，但这绝对不是
requirement you could route to any
要求您可以路由到任何
static URI you want - sure sure
您想要的静态URI-确定
okay that makes no sense um okay I think
好吧，那没有意义，我想
we've got everything we've got a bunch
我们拥有了一切，我们拥有了一堆
of nice feedback for you and some
为您和一些人提供了很好的反馈
ratings and yes in terms of votes folks
评分和赞成票的人
now is the time to go to your panel and
现在是时候进入您的小组了
your you're voting panel in the your
您在您的投票面板中
polling panel excuse me in the web user
网络用户请问投票小组
interface let me know what you want to
界面让我知道你想要什么
hear about in the future this will help
将来知道这会有所帮助
us program what kind of topics you want
我们计划您想要什么样的主题
to hear about and on seeing a very
听到并看到非常
consistent tribulus trend recently so we
最近的趋势一致，所以我们
are very actively looking forward to
非常期待
more webinars on spring cloud function
有关Spring Cloud功能的更多网络研讨会
I'm sure your client side and also a
我确定您的客户方也是
really cool project called risk where
真的很酷的项目叫做风险
we're working on the server side of that
我们正在服务器端
function execution environment so we'll
函数执行环境，所以我们将
be we'll be doing some webinar on that
是的，我们将对此进行一些网络研讨会
soon make make no mistake
很快就不要犯错
so cool um let's see Ryan anything uh it
好酷，嗯，让我们看看Ryan
doesn't look like there's any last
看起来好像没有什么了
questions so I think we can wrap it up
问题，我想我们可以总结一下
anything else you would like to to say
您想说的其他话
before we call it a wrap
在我们将其称为包装之前
no just want to thank everyone for
不只是想感谢大家
attending and then yeah look forward to
参加，然后是很期待
all great feedback on upcoming release
关于即将发布的版本的所有很好的反馈
awesome okay Ryan thank for your time
太好了，瑞安，谢谢您的时间
and folks remember um
和人们记得嗯
register for spring one before July 31st
在7月31日之前注册 Spring 一
for 200 dollars off and we hope to see
为200美元的折扣，我们希望看到
you at the event we're targeting between
您在我们的目标是
three and four thousand people this year
今年三四千人
it's going to be pretty epic arm ten
这将是史诗般的十臂
tracks amazing presenters all kinds of
跟踪各种惊人的演示者
fun stuff so hope to see you there
好玩的东西，希望能在那里见到你
alright everyone have a wonderful day
好吧，每个人都有美好的一天
and thanks for joining us
感谢您加入我们